Guide to the Portland Brewing Company Records 1984-2021
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- Portland Brewing Company, 1991-2014; Series 2
  - Building plans and promotional materials, 1992-1996 (Map-folder 1)
    Portland Brewing Company tenant improvements building plans (Arthur James Engineer, 2 pages), early schema of product flow through the Portland facility, poster for MacTarnahan's beer showing Mac MacTarnahan in running attire with beer medals around his neck, mounted article about Portland Brewing Company.
  - Photographs, 1997 and undated (Box-folder 11.01)
    Group picture in Portland Brewing pub, picture of building and people working in the brewery.
  - Marketing and promotion materials, undated (Box-folder 11.02)
    Various posters including Portland Brewing Unipiper Hazy IPA poster, signed and dated 2019, and Oregon Honey Beer, Portland Brewing Company metal sign,
- Hart Brewing, 1984-1993; Series 3
  Scrapbook with items that reflect the growth and changes in the company in the first years. Included are drafts of company description and purpose statements; photographs of events, company offices, employees, and equipment; coasters and product table tents; invitations (e.g. Northwest Regional Wine Tastings); fliers for tastings (e.g. Western Washington Beverage tasting at Rays Boathouse) or events (e.g. The Great Northwest Beer Festival); correspondence related to events or donations (e.g. Bellevue's Peter Puget Festival and The Xerces Society); advertisements; and menus. Also included are news clippings by authors such as Vince Cottone and Fred Eckhardt with highlighted sections for information about Hart, including the opening of Hart Brewing, beer releases, regional sales, articles about Beth Hartwell and Tom Baune; and information about their sale of the brewery in 1989. This scrapbook was disassembled for preservation and access.
  - Marketing and promotional items, circa 1993 (Box-folder 10.25)
  - Scrapbook, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 10.26)
    Menus, coasters, labels, event invitations, correspondence.
  - Scrapbook pictures, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 10.27)
    30 photographs of events, brewing facilities, and brewers.
  - Scrapbook news clippings, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 10.28)
  - Ephemera, 1995 (Box-folder 11.03)
    Plaque for Hart Brewery and Pub from Seattle Times and “Lads of Seattle, 2034” parody poster.
- Pyramid Breweries, 1997-2010; Series 4
  Marketing and promotional items including labels and posters, a training manual for new employees, and news clippings about the company and products.
  - Marketing and promotional items, 1997-2007 (Box-folder 10.29)
  - Newsclippings, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 10.30)
  - Training manual, 2010 (Box-folder 10.31)